aiaa.org 2019-10-23

# Privacy Policy | AIAA

AIAA collects personally identifiable information when you place an order for an AIAA product or service; submit an abstract or paper for publication; subscribe to a journal, newsletter, or our magazine; register for a conference; apply for membership; make a donation; or otherwise participate in the activities of the Institute. We may also collect personally identifiable information when you send an e-mail, and we may collect demographic and personal interest information when it is available, using web analytics. In each case, our objective in collecting this information is to learn more about you so that we can serve you better. 

If you choose to make a payment to us, we may collect certain information from you, including address, mailing preferences, email, etc. so that we can accurately complete the transaction. In cases where we use third-party service providers for payment processing, we do not collect or maintain your payment card information.

We also collect information volunteered by users, such as survey responses. This information is kept confidential by AIAA and is used internally to improve our products, services, communications, and customer service operations.

If we intend to use any information we collect from you in a manner that is not consistent with this policy, you will be informed of this anticipated use in advance of when the information is collected, or we will obtain your consent subsequent to collecting the information but before the information is used. 

Our partnerships with outside vendors and third-party service providers are intended to enhance our own processes, products, and services and to streamline transactions. Internet systems and services provided by our vendor partners that are accessible through our websites have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. You are advised to read the privacy policies of external sites made available by our service providers and partners before disclosing any personally identifiable information. Contact them directly if you have questions. Additionally, AIAA is not responsible for content or activities that may be available through third-party links that are included on our websites or through social media. AIAA’s privacy policy does not apply to any personally identifiable information collected by such a third party, even if access to their products and services was achieved through an AIAA website or other communication.
